Cihangir Bozdogan

Front End Developer

London E16 4NJ bozdogan.cihangir@gmail.com +44 7342759900

Frontend Developer based in London. Nowadays, mostly focused on development, but I like to explore new visual trends. I have hands-on practical experience in developing designs for modern websites for over 7 years.

Work Experience

Cofounder

Monitorables - London February 2020 to March 2021

Monitorables is an online market research store aiming specifically at e-commerce industry. I involved handling the business side of the things as well as maintaining the website.

Front End Developer

Social Swag Digital Agency - London June 2015 to August 2020

Social Swag is a digital marketing company that focuses on creating content for the web. My duty was to maintain the custom-built content management software. Adding new features, fixing bugs, maintenance of a large codebase using Vue, React and Sass, and collaborating with team members using Git, TeamGantt, Asana, Slack.

Web Developer & Graphic Designer

Salon Guru - London January 2015 to February 2016

Building websites, landing pages, html emails, designing banners and social media posts.

Technologies: Html, Css, Javascript, Jquery, Wordpress, MySql, Cpanel, Photoshop, Illustrator, MailChimp.

Web Developer & Graphic Designer

Master Legal Services - London November 2014 to June 2015

Maintaining company's website, email marketing, SEO, graphic design, social media posts, Google analytics.

Technologies: Html, Css, Javascript, Jquery, Wordpress, Cpanel, Photoshop, Illustrator.

Education

Bachelor's in Computer drafting and design

European University of Lefke - Lefke

July 2011 to September 2013

A-Level or equivalent in Electrical technician

Yildirim Technology College - Ankara

October 2008 to June 2012

- Git
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- React
- Php
- Sql
- vue
- Linux
- HTML5
- Jquery
- Node.js
- Redux
- Nextjs
- Typescript
- Nuxt
- Sass
- Javascript
- CSS
- Responsive Web Design
- Front End
- UI
- Front-End
- CSS3
- Node
- Bootstrap

Languages

- English Fluent
- Turkish Fluent

Links

https://cihangir.dev

https://github.com/jankoboz/